

Contact

Phone

+421 918 300 905

Email

tutkova.j@gmail.com

Address

Okružná 58, Michalovce, 071 01

Languages

English B2

German C1

Driving license

В

Expertise

Basics of C#

Basics of Python

Basics of JavaScript

HTML and CSS

LATEX

Unity

Blender

Matlab

Inkscape

Canva

Mailchimp

Game Design

ServiceNow

CAD

SketchUp

Jana Tutková

Student of Computer graphics and Geometry at the Comenius University Bratislava

I am a diligent and organized team player with problem-solving abilities. I have gained a lot of experience and soft skills during my years of volunteering. My hobbies include volleyball, instrumental music and book reading.

Experience

2023

Siemens Healthineers

Summer Development Academy

I was attending student academy with focus on ServiceNow platform in summer 2023.

2022 - 2024

Hemisféra

Parttime Lecturer

Hemisféra provides comprehensive education in the field of digital game creation. I have participated in the GameCamp children's camp many times. My main task was to teach the children to come up with the design and graphics of the game, which they even programmed at the camp.

2022

PS:Sunrise

Intern

I completed an internship in a marketing-event company.

Volunteering

2021 - 2024

VIDES

Volunteer

2019 - 2023

Laura, združenie mladých

Presidency

2015 - 2024

Domka - združenie saleziánskej mládeže and Laura, združenie mladých **Animator and organizer of events for children and youth**

Education

Comenius University Bratislava

Faculty of Mathematics, Physics and Informatics

2022 - 2024

Master: Computer Graphics and Geometry

2019 - 2022

Bachelor: Mathematics

2015 - 2019

Pavol Horov Gymnasium, Michalovce

During high school, I managed to get a German language certificate DSD I and DSD II. I participated in the Die Schulbrücke project with a 10-day stay in Weimar, Germany. I took part in the SOČ with theme Musical Tunings, with which I won 3rd place in the regional round. I also took part in several team physics competitions, for example Fyzikláni online and I played the piano in the school band.

2017 - 2019

School for animators

Completed course with certification in the scope of 4 weekends.